<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Memori</string>
    <string name="TitleSabeWords">Save your words</string>
    <string name="ContentSaveWords">Enter the word you want and then its translation. We will remember it for you when you want!</string>
    <string name="textCampOrgSave">Enter your question</string>
    <string name="textCampTradSave">Enter your answer</string>
    <string name="textbtnsave">SAVE</string>
    <string name="TitleEva">Practice your questions</string>
    <string name="ContentEva">Evaluate yourself! Try reviewing the questions you have saved so you don\'t forget them.</string>
    <string name="textCampTradEva">There are no questions</string>
    <string name="textbtneva">EVALUATE</string>
    <string name="ContentMem">Save your phrases, definitions, words, etc. and we will remind you of them when you want.</string>
    <string name="TitleMem">Save your memories</string>
    <string name="textCampMem">Save your memories here</string>
    <string name="textbtnMem">SAVE</string>
    <string name="switchtext">Questions</string>
    <string name="switchMem">Memories</string>
    <string name="titlelistW">List of words</string>
    <string name="titlelistM">"List of Memories "</string>
    <string name="setToastTitle">Temporary reminder</string>
    <string name="settoastcontent">Show a toast with the inserted questions and answers. Set your time interval.</string>
    <string name="setFloatTitle">Floating window</string>
    <string name="setFloatContent">Show a pop-up window, guess your question or press the exit button to close the window. Set your time interval.</string>
    <string name="setMemTitle">Floating memories</string>
    <string name="setBubFloatTitle">Floating bubble</string>
    <string name="setMemContent">Show a pop-up card that will remind you of your memories. Set your time interval.</string>
    <string name="setBubFloatCont">Show a bubble that allows a window to emerge to save words while using other applications.</string>
    <string name="setbubmemtitle">Memory bubble.</string>
    <string name="setbubmemcont">Show a bubble that allows a card to emerge to save your memories while using other applications.</string>
    <string name="helptoast">You can define the time in which you want to be reminded of the questions and answers you have entered through a toast that will appear at the bottom of your screen while using other applications, you must add questions to enable this function.</string>
    <string name="helpfloating">You can define the time in which you want to practice your questions even when you are using other applications through a pop-up window that will show you your question and close if you answer correctly or by pressing the close button. Add your questions to enable this functionality.</string>
    <string name="helpmemorias">You can define the time in which you want a card to appear on your screen showing one of the memories you have saved while using other applications, you must add memories to enable this function.</string>
    <string name="helpbubfloat">A permanent bubble will appear on your screen that when pressed will open a window that will allow you to save your questions while using other applications and you can close the window by pressing the bubble again. You can close the bubble by quickly swiping down.</string>
    <string name="helpbubmem">A permanent bubble will appear on your screen that when pressed will open a card that will allow you to save your memories while using other applications and you can close the card by pressing the bubble again. You can close the bubble by quickly swiping down.</string>
    <string name="permisionTitle">Screen overlay permission is required</string>
    <string name="permissonContent">Enable Allow display over other apps from the settings</string>
    <string name="btnpermision">Open settings</string>
    <string name="helpSave">The questions section allows you to enter a question and an answer made by you, these will be displayed on your screen at a time interval set by you in the settings section.</string>
    <string name="helpEva">The evaluation section allows you to practice your questions, that is, you must enter the answer to the question you saved yourself and if it is correct you can move on to your next question</string>
    <string name="helpCard">The memory section allows you to save words, phrases, etc. that do not have an answer. You can set the time interval you want to be reminded of in the settings section.</string>
    <string name="helpList">The list section allows you to view, edit, and delete the questions and memories you have saved. They are divided into two sections, which you can see by pressing the switch at the top.</string>
    <string name="toastSave">You must fill in the fields</string>
    <string name="toastsave2">Word saved correctly!</string>
    <string name="toastCard">You must fill in the text fields</string>
    <string name="toastcard2">Word saved correctly!</string>
    <string name="toastServicefloat">No words were found</string>
    <string name="toastServicefloat2">Time equal to 0 is not valid</string>
    <string name="dialogtitle">Do you want to delete the word?</string>
    <string name="dialogY">YES</string>
    <string name="dialogN">NO</string>
    <string name="btnEstablecer">SET</string>
    <string name="btnCancel">CANCEL</string>
    <string name="androidVersion">Lo sentimos, tu version de android no te permite usar esta función</string>
    <string name="ejecutServ">Memory in execution</string>
    <string name="notifyToast">Reminder set</string>
    <string name="notifyMemServ">Memories set</string>
    <string name="notifyMemSave">Floating Bubble set</string>
    <string name="floatingWindow">Floating Window set</string>
    <string name="notifyBubble">Bubble memory set</string>
</resources>